Music Box Alpha Privacy Policy

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their

'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and

information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify,

contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy

carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your

Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our website or app?

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email

address, mailing address or other details to help you with your experience.

When do we collect information?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to a

newsletter, fill out a form or enter information on our site.

How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our

newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site

features in the following ways:

• To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings

in which you are most interested.

• To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.

• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.

• To quickly process your transactions.

• To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.

How do we protect your information?

We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.

An external PCI compliant payment gateway handles all CC transactions.

We use regular Malware Scanning.

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited

number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the

information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure

Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order, enters, submits, or accesses

their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our

servers.

Do we use 'cookies'?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive

through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to

recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to

help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us

understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you

with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site

interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

We use cookies to:

• Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.

• Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site

experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this

information on our behalf.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to

turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since each browser is a little different,

look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If users disable cookies in their browser:

If you turn cookies off, some of the features that make your site experience more efficient may not

function properly.

Third-party disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information.

Third-party links

We do not include or offer third-party products or services on our website.

We have implemented the following:

We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics

cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers

together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions

as they relate to our website.

Opting out:

Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page.

Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the

Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

California Online Privacy Protection Act

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a

privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the

United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable

Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating

exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being

shared.

See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-

caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf

According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:

Users can visit our site anonymously.

Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum, on the

first significant page after entering our website.

Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy' and can easily be found on the page specified above.

You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes:

• On our Privacy Policy Page

You can change your personal information:

• By emailing us

How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?

We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track

(DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?

It's also important to note that we do not allow third-party behavioral tracking.

COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the

Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission,

United States' consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators

of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.

Fair Information Practices

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the

concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around

the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented

is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action,

should a data breach occur:

We will notify you via email

• Within 1 business day

We will notify the users via in-site notification

• Within 1 business day

We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally

pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This

principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that

individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-

compliance by data processors.

CAN SPAM Act

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for

commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and

spells out tough penalties for violations.

We collect your email address in order to:

• Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions

• Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders.

• Send you additional information related to your product and/or service

• Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has

occurred.

To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:

• Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.

• Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.

• Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.

• Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.

• Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.

• Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails:

• Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email and we will promptly remove you from all

correspondence.

Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.

https://www.musicboxalpha.com

PO Box 577632

Modesto, CA 95357

United States

support@unbrokensoftware.com

Last Edited on 2019-01-25
